presszel.com 2016-01-21

# Privacy - Presszel

Your privacy is important to PRESSZEL.  This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that PRESSZEL collects, and the ways in which PRESSZEL uses that personal information.

Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.

**Scope:  **This privacy policy applies only to the Site. This policy does not apply to information collected through any other website or to the practices of companies that the PRESSZEL does not control. Please note that the Site may contain links to other websites. For example, if you click on an advertisement on the Site and link to another website, then this privacy policy will not apply to any information collected on that website. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites, and we recommend that you read the privacy policies of each website that you visit.

**PRESSZEL may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:**

-Information about your use of this website (including your computer’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, your browser type and operating system, the web pages you were visiting immediately before and after you came to the Site, activities within community discussions, web pages and advertisements that you view, and links that you click on, within the Site, your bandwidth speed and information about the software programs that are installed on your computer, aggregated data about email click-through rates and user video viewing;

-Standard server log information and information collected through HTML cookies, Flash cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies.

-Information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website.

-Information about transactions carried out over this website.

-Information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services.

-Any other information that you send to PRESSZEL.

**PRESSZEL may use your personal information to:**

-Administer this website.

-Personalize the website for you.

-Enable your access to and use of the website services.

-Publish information about you on the website.

-Send to you products that you purchase.

-Supply to you services that you purchase.

-Send to you statements and invoices.

-Collect payments from you.

-Send you marketing communications.

Where PRESSZEL discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, PRESSZEL may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

**Securing your data**

PRESSZEL will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

PRESSZEL will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers.

Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website will be protected by encryption technology.

**  Cross-border data transfers**

Information that PRESSZEL collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which PRESSZEL operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world.

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

**  Updating this statement**

PRESSZEL may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

**Other websites**

This website contains links to other websites.  PRESSZEL is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

**Contact PRESSZEL**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or PRESSZEL treatment of your personal information, please write to: support@Presszel.com
